https://www.theacpa.org/privacy-policy/

Already a member? Log In or Sign Up
Research and Clinical TrialsConditions & TreatmentsHow to Communicate Symptoms to HCPQuality of Life ScaleConditions A-ZTreatments A-ZPain Management ToolsCommunication ToolsTracking ToolsMedCard PDFBack Pain MapCARE Card (How to take your medications)Cluster Headaches Conversation GuideDaily Activity ChecklistDPN Pain MapFibro LogFibro Pain MapFollow Up From Your VisitHead Pain MapPain LogArthritis Ability ChartMigraine Conversation GuideOIC LogMigraine LogOpioid Induced Constipation Graphical ToolPain Log Phone AppPrepare For Your Healthcare VisitQuality of Life ScaleWhere Does It Hurt? / Nerve ManQuality of Life Scale – SpanishInteractive MapsPDF Graphical ToolsPhone AppsFrom Patient to PersonSelf-Management SkillsBasic RightsGoing to the ERHow to PrepareWhat to Expect“Why do I have to wait so long?”What Not to ExpectWhen You See the DoctorThe Importance of Following UpPain Management ProgramsAssessmentCommunication – Importance of Using ACPA Communication ToolsEducationProgram OutcomesConclusionVideosCommunication/EducationConditions/TreatmentsSupportRelaxation AudioFAQsResourcesHealth ConditionsLife ResourcesProfessional GroupsHelpful ReadingSurveysTaking CareMigraine HeadachesOICHaving a Plan for an Opioid EmergencyAccess and Attitudes GloballyResource Guide to Chronic Pain TreatmentsResource Guide to Chronic Pain ManagementConsumer Guidelines for Low Back PainMore About MedicationsThe Art of Pain ManagementLiving With PainMusic to Help You RelaxPain AwarenessPartners for Understanding PainPartners ListMediaPain Awareness ToolkitsSeptember is Pain Awareness MonthUp Coming Events (Calendar)Quick LinksDonateShopLinking
PolicyThe American Chronic Pain AssociationAbout UsSupport GroupsBoard of DirectorsAdvisory BoardPartners & ContributorsChronicles & Updates-Staying ConnectedArchivesACPA NewsletterACPA HistorySupport ACPAContact Us
Research and Clinical TrialsConditions & TreatmentsHow to Communicate Symptoms to HCPQuality of Life ScaleConditions A-ZTreatments A-ZPain Management ToolsCommunication ToolsTracking ToolsMedCard PDFBack Pain MapCARE Card (How to take your medications)Cluster Headaches Conversation GuideDaily Activity ChecklistDPN Pain MapFibro LogFibro Pain MapFollow Up From Your VisitHead Pain MapPain LogArthritis Ability ChartMigraine Conversation GuideOIC LogMigraine LogOpioid Induced Constipation Graphical ToolPain Log Phone AppPrepare For Your Healthcare VisitQuality of Life ScaleWhere Does It Hurt? / Nerve ManQuality of Life Scale – SpanishInteractive MapsPDF Graphical ToolsPhone AppsFrom Patient to PersonSelf-Management SkillsBasic RightsGoing to the ERHow to PrepareWhat to Expect“Why do I have to wait so long?”What Not to ExpectWhen You See the DoctorThe Importance of Following UpPain Management ProgramsAssessmentCommunication – Importance of Using ACPA Communication ToolsEducationProgram OutcomesConclusionVideosCommunication/EducationConditions/TreatmentsSupportRelaxation AudioFAQsResourcesHealth ConditionsLife ResourcesProfessional GroupsHelpful ReadingSurveysTaking CareMigraine HeadachesOICHaving a Plan for an Opioid EmergencyAccess and Attitudes GloballyResource Guide to Chronic Pain TreatmentsResource Guide to Chronic Pain ManagementConsumer Guidelines for Low Back PainMore About MedicationsThe Art of Pain ManagementLiving With PainMusic to Help You RelaxPain AwarenessPartners for Understanding PainPartners ListMediaPain Awareness ToolkitsSeptember is Pain Awareness MonthUp Coming Events (Calendar)Quick LinksDonateShopLinking
PolicyThe American Chronic Pain AssociationAbout UsSupport GroupsBoard of DirectorsAdvisory BoardPartners & ContributorsChronicles & Updates-Staying ConnectedArchivesACPA NewsletterACPA HistorySupport ACPAContact UsThe American Chronic Pain AssociationAbout UsSupport GroupsBoard of DirectorsAdvisory BoardPartners & ContributorsChronicles & Updates-Staying ConnectedArchivesACPA NewsletterACPA HistorySupport ACPA Contact UsThe American Chronic Pain AssociationAbout UsSupport GroupsBoard of DirectorsAdvisory BoardPartners & ContributorsChronicles & Updates-Staying ConnectedArchivesACPA NewsletterACPA HistorySupport ACPA Contact Us Homepage > Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyACPA is committed to protecting the privacy of its website users. We occasionally request that you provide personal information, such as your name, address, email address, telephone number, and other information from which your identity can be discerned. ACPA does not rent, sell, lend, or give personally identifiable information collected from you on its web site to marketers or other parties. We may disclose personal information in response to a subpoena or when we believe in good faith that the law requires. We do record how often various pages are visited to help us improve our content and better serve people with an interest in chronic pain. Our On-Line Catalog is hosted by Yahoo! Store and is governed by the Yahoo! Privacy Policy. Please see the Yahoo! Privacy Policy for more information about privacy when ordering on line.We take your privacy very seriously. We do not sell any contact information of any of our users, at any time. Any data that we may collect is kept private and only used for internal information purposes, and only the ACPA administrators can access any user data.The American Chronic Pain Association does not participate in any sort of advertising or make unsolicited phone calls.
If you receive an unsolicited phone call from someone claiming to be the American Chronic Pain Association, please report it to www.FTC.gov.
For more information, please read our Privacy Policy.The America’s Best Charities Seal of Excellence is awarded to charitable organizations that meet the highest standards of public accountability, program effectiveness, and cost effectiveness..GoldStar Seal of Transparency.We comply with the HONcode standard for trustworthy health information: Verify here.Terms & ConditionsPrivacy PolicyAdvertising PolicyLanguage DisclaimerEndorsement PolicyThis web page is made possible from donations from our members and the people who visit the site.
